cpvad.com 2014-06-25

# DirectCPV Pay Per View PPV Cost Per View CPV Contextual Online Advertising Privacy Policy

Directcpv Technologies, Inc., a British Columbia corporation, and its subsidiaries and affiliated entities (collectively, "Directcpv" or "Company") is committed to protecting the privacy of our customer's personal information and expects that its publishers will take similar precautions to protect their end-users. This Website Privacy Policy (this "Privacy Policy") applies with respect to the information that we collect (directly or indirectly through our publishers and/or advertisers) through the use from the Company Website, located at Directcpv.com, and explains how we collect, use and disclose your personal information in connection with our services. Amendments to this Policy will be posted at this URL. Your continued use of this site following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance thereof. While the Company may update you of any changes to its Privacy Policy, it is your obligation to review the terms of this Privacy Policy and stay current therewith.

**1\. INFORMATION COLLECTED**

We collect non-personally identifiable information in a number of ways, including tracking your activities through search terms, internet browsing, computer settings or most-recently visited URL. Personally identifiable information is personal information about you including your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number, and that which is not otherwise publicly available. We may also ask you to provide certain non-personally identifiable information about yourself, such as your age, household income, buying preferences, etc. Personally identifiable information about you is collected when you voluntarily submit such information to us, by, for example, filling out a survey or registration form. We may combine personal information collected from you with information from other Company services or third parties to provide a better user experience, including customizing content for you.

We do not gather personal financial information, including credit card numbers, passwords, or login names, however, our advertisers, partners, publishers or affiliates may obtain such information through being redirected to their sites. In such instances, the Company shall not be held responsible and is expressly released for any misuse or disclosure of information provided by an end user disclosed using any site that is not maintained or owned by the Company.

**2\. USE OF INFORMATION**

In general, we will only use the information you provide to us (directly or indirectly) for the purpose for which such information was provided (i.e. search terms will be matched with results we believe are reasonably related to such terms). We may also use this information to deliver to you information about our company or the companies of our advertisers and promotional material from some of our partners, advertisers and affiliates, trend analysis, pattern detection, and site administration. Your information may also be used to contact you when necessary and may be shared with other companies that may want to contact you with offers consistent with your stated preferences. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings from Company and other entities by following the instructions set forth in the opt-out section below.

Non-personal demographic and profile data is used to tailor your experience at our site, showing you content we think you might be interested in. This information may also be shared with advertisers on an aggregate non-personal basis. We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services. The Company may also disclose your information upon a transfer or sale to another entity of the Company or upon any other corporate reorganization.

**3\. USE OF IP ADDRESSES**

We may use your IP Address information as part of our effort to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website.

**4\. USE OF COOKIES**

Cookies are an industry standard used by most major Websites. When you view our Website (or the Websites of our advertisers, partners and affiliates) we or they might store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Cookies do not spy on you or otherwise invade your privacy, and they cannot invade your hard drive and steal information. Rather, they help you navigate a Website as easily as possible. We use cookies to improve the quality of our services, deliver content specific to your interests and to prevent you from reentering all your registration data at each connection.

We may use an outside advertisement server company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. Through banner ads the advertisement server company may set and access their cookies on your computer. We do not have access to information that would confirm the use of cookies by the advertisement server company. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policy, not this one. You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features may not function properly as a result.

**5\. SECURITY**

Our site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as "absolute security" on the Internet, we make good faith efforts to take every step to ensure the safety of your personal information, whenever reasonably possible.

**6\. OTHER WEBSITES; LINKS**

Our Website or the links we provide to related results contains links to other Websites. Because this Policy only applies to the Company Website itself and not linked Websites, you should examine the privacy policy of any other Websites that you access from the Company Website. The Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other Websites.

**7\. FOR MORE INFORMATION/UPDATE**

The Company allows its users the option to change or modify information previously provided. This may be done through the following methods:

E-mail the information to support@directcpv.com.  
Contact us by telephone (866) 984-6278 or by mail: 1270-1188 Georgia Street West, Vancouver, BC V6E 4A2, Canada to advise us of any changes.

Unfortunately, to the extent that such information is also stored in other databases, we cannot always ensure that such corrections or deletions will reach the other databases. We will use all reasonable efforts to ensure that your information is removed from or corrected in our records.

**8\. CHOICE; OPT OUT**

You may opt-out of receiving communications from our partners, and from us, by the following means:

**Send an e-mail to support@directcpv.com.  
Contact us by telephone (866) 984-6278 or by mail: 1270-1188 Georgia Street West, Vancouver, BC V6E 4A2, Canada to advise us of your desire to opt out.**

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Company service, such as service announcements and administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them absent a cancellation of services with the Company.

**Contacting us:**

If you have any questions about this Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, you can contact us at support@directcpv.com.
